{"qid": "0", "question": "Who penned the paper \"sirt2 inhibition activates hypoxia inducible factor 1\u03b1 signaling and mediates neuronal survival?\"", "answer": "Nobuko Matsushita, Taku Kaitsuka, Masayuki Matsushita"}
{"qid": "1", "question": "Who penned the paper \"instantaneous and permanent photoionization?\"", "answer": "E. B. Krissinel, Nikita N. Lukzen, Anatoly I. Burshtein, Oleg A. Igoshin"}
{"qid": "2", "question": "Who penned the paper \"complex rare earth aluminum hydrides mechanochemical preparation crystal structure and potential for hydrogen storage?\"", "answer": "Borislav Bogdanovi\u0107, Wenhao Sun, Claudia Weidenthaler, Michael Felderhoff, Chris Wolverton, Andre Pommerin, Ferdi Sch\u00fcth"}
{"qid": "3", "question": "Do you know who the authors of \"asymmetric and independent contribution of the second transmembrane segment 12 residues to diliganded gating of acetylcholine receptor channels a single channel study with choline as the agonist\" are?", "answer": "Claudio Grosman, Anthony Auerbach"}
{"qid": "4", "question": "Who are the authors of paper \"on the stability of the extracellular hemoglobin of glossoscolex paulistus in two iron oxidation states in the presence of urea?\" ", "answer": "Patr\u00edcia S. Santiago, Francisco A.O. Carvalho, Marcel Tabak"}
{"qid": "5", "question": "Who are the authors of paper \"thorium iv molecular clusters with a hexanuclear th core?\" ", "answer": "David A. Dixon, Lynda Soderholm, Richard E. Wilson, Monica Vasiliu, Karah E. Knope"}
{"qid": "6", "question": "Do you know who the authors of \"chemistry eluting the tag\" are?", "answer": "J. S. Yeston"}
{"qid": "7", "question": "Can you tell me the authors of the paper titled \"reactions of chlorine atoms with a series of aromatic hydrocarbons?\"", "answer": "Janet Arey, Lin Wang, Roger Atkinson"}
{"qid": "8", "question": "Can you tell me the authors of the paper titled \"m fluorotyrosine substitution in \u03b2 galactosidase evidence for the existence of a catalytically active tyrosine?\"", "answer": "Ian M. Armitage, Mark Ring, Reuben E. Huber"}
{"qid": "9", "question": "Do you know who the authors of \"efficient assembly of iminodicarboxamides by a truly four component reaction\" are?", "answer": "Tadamichi Nagashima, Kareem Khoury, Alexander D\u00f6mling, Mantosh K. Sinha, Eberhardt Herdtweck"}
{"qid": "10", "question": "Where is the paper \"nickel catalyzed denitrogenative annulation reactions of 1 2 3 benzotriazin 4 3h ones with 1 3 dienes and alkenes\" published?", "answer": "journal of organic chemistry"}
{"qid": "11", "question": "Where is the paper \"self assembled monolayers on polymer surfaces kinetics functionalization and photopatterning\" published?", "answer": "langmuir"}
{"qid": "12", "question": "Which publication features the paper titled \"simultaneous detection of trichothecenes and rosenonolactone in grape juice and wine by capillary gas chromatography\"?", "answer": "journal of chromatography a"}
{"qid": "13", "question": "Can you tell me the publication where the paper \"aqueous intermolecular diels alder chemistry novel products derived from substituted benzoquinone diene carboxylate adducts via tandem michael reactions\" was published?", "answer": "tetrahedron letters"}
{"qid": "14", "question": "Can you tell me the publication where the paper \"regenerative and non regenerative calcium transients in hamster eggs triggered by inositol 1 4 5 trisphosphate\" was published?", "answer": "the journal of physiology"}
{"qid": "15", "question": "Can you tell me the publication where the paper \"electrochemical reduction of pristinamycin ia and related streptogramins in aqueous acidic medium\" was published?", "answer": "tetrahedron"}
{"qid": "16", "question": "In which publication can I find the paper \"n 6 methyl 2 pyridyl acrylamide a case of amide hydrolysis without the assistance of acid or base in the synthesis of water driven h bonded polymeric chains\"?", "answer": "tetrahedron letters"}
{"qid": "17", "question": "Can you tell me the publication where the paper \"binding of inhibitory aromatic amino acids to streptomyces griseus aminopeptidase\" was published?", "answer": "journal of biological chemistry"}
{"qid": "18", "question": "Which publication features the paper titled \"deuterium isotope effects in 13c nmr spectroscopy stereochemical assignment of monodeuteriated allylic alcohols\"?", "answer": "tetrahedron letters"}
{"qid": "19", "question": "In which publication can I find the paper \"preparation of \u03b1 deuterated l amino acids using e coli b it7 a cells containing tryptophanase\"?", "answer": "tetrahedron letters"}
{"qid": "20", "question": "Who collaborates with author David T. Cramb to write paper \"measuring properties of nanoparticles in embryonic blood vessels towards a physicochemical basis for nanotoxicity\"?", "answer": "Yiota Gregoriou, Kristin Yaehne, Aisling A. Clancy"}
{"qid": "21", "question": "Who has been working with author Amitabha Sinha to write the paper \"a computational study investigating the energetics and kinetics of the hnco ch3 2nh reaction catalyzed by a single water molecule\"?", "answer": "Joseph S. Francisco, Chanin B. Tangtartharakul, Manoj Kumar, Arathala Parandaman"}
{"qid": "22", "question": "Who are the collaborators of author Robert N. Clayton in writing the paper \"potassium isotope cosmochemistry genetic implications of volatile element depletion\"?", "answer": "Munir Humayun"}
{"qid": "23", "question": "Who has been working with author Can Wang to write the paper \"enantiomer specific bioaccumulation and depuration of hexabromocyclododecanes in zebrafish danio rerio\"?", "answer": "Changzhou Yan, Miaomiao Du, Xian Zhang, Lifeng Lin"}
{"qid": "24", "question": "Who has been working with author A.V. Domanskaya to write the paper \"microscopic roots of alcohol ketone demixing infrared spectroscopy of methanol acetone clusters\"?", "answer": "Martin A. Suhm, F. Kollipost"}
{"qid": "25", "question": "Who co-wrote the paper \"ionization state of pyridoxal 5 phosphate in d serine dehydratase dialkylglycine decarboxylase and tyrosine phenol lyase and the influence of monovalent cations as inferred by 31p nmr spectroscopy\" with author Klaus D. Schnackerz?", "answer": "Michael D. Toney, John W. Keller, Robert S. Phillips"}
{"qid": "26", "question": "Who co-wrote the paper \"spiroketal based diphosphine ligands in pd catalyzed asymmetric allylic amination of morita baylis hillman adducts exceptionally high efficiency and new mechanism\" with author Kuiling Ding?", "answer": "Zheng Wang, Zhaobin Han, Peihua Guo, Xubin Wang, Xiaoming Wang"}
{"qid": "27", "question": "Who collaborates with author Amalendu Chandra to write paper \"born oppenheimer molecular dynamics simulations of a bromate ion in water reveal its dual kosmotropic and chaotropic behavior\"?", "answer": "Bikramjit Sharma"}
{"qid": "28", "question": "Who partnered with author Ligang Lin to produce the paper \"adsorption and solvent desorption behavior of ion exchanged modified y zeolites for sulfur removal and for fuel cell applications\"?", "answer": "Fuwei Lu, Hongyu Zhang, Yuzhong Zhang"}
{"qid": "29", "question": "Who collaborates with author Ronald Pethig to write paper \"applications of a new optical technique for measuring the dielectrophoretic behaviour of micro organisms\"?", "answer": "Jonathan A.R. Price, Julian P.H. Burt"}
{"qid": "30", "question": "Who is the author of both the papers \"toward hexaphenylethane structure and decomposition of crystalline triphenylmethyl iodide\" and \"cure reaction pathways of bismaleimide polymers a solid state 15n nmr investigation\"?", "answer": "Brett A. Cowans"}
{"qid": "31", "question": "Who is the author of both the papers \"decreased activity of the antioxidant heme oxygenase enzyme implications in ischemia and in alzheimer s disease\" and \"catalytically inactive heme oxygenase 2 mutant is cytoprotective\"?", "answer": "Sylvain Dor\u00e9"}
{"qid": "32", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"inhibition of energy transfer between conjugated polymer chains in host guest nanocomposites generates white photo and electroluminescence\" and paper \"bulk synthesis of inorganic fullerene like ms2 m mo w from the respective trioxides and the reaction mechanism\"?", "answer": "Gitti L. Frey"}
{"qid": "33", "question": "Who composed the papers \"a pilot study on the assessment of trace organic contaminants including pharmaceuticals and personal care products from on site wastewater treatment systems along skaneateles lake in new york state usa\" and \"simultaneous analysis of select pharmaceuticals and personal care products in fish tissue using pressurized liquid extraction combined with silica gel cleanup\"?", "answer": "Bikram Subedi"}
{"qid": "34", "question": "Who composed the papers \"ovariectomy disregulates osteoblast and osteoclast formation through the t cell receptor cd40 ligand\" and \"dry powder inhalation of macromolecules using novel peg co polyester microparticle carriers\"?", "answer": "Hesham M. Tawfeek"}
{"qid": "35", "question": "Who is the author of both the papers \"cmpo calix 4 arenes with spacer containing intramolecular hydrogen bonding effect of local rigidification on solvent extraction toward f block elements\" and \"mild periodic acid flux and hydrothermal methods for the synthesis of crystalline f element bearing iodate compounds\"?", "answer": "Ning Liu"}
{"qid": "36", "question": "Who is the author of both the papers \"molecular identification of hspa8 as an accessory protein of a hyperpolarization activated chloride channel from rat pulmonary vein cardiomyocytes\" and \"time dependent block of the slowly activating delayed rectifier k current by chromanol 293b in guinea pig ventricular cells\"?", "answer": "Kyoichi Ono"}
{"qid": "37", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"more meanders and sandwiches\" and paper \"structure of collagen\"?", "answer": "Guy Riddihough"}
{"qid": "38", "question": "Who penned the papers \"sticking and recombination of the sih3 radical on hydrogenated amorphous silicon the catalytic effect of diborane\" and \"surface reactions during the a si h growth in the diode and triode glow discharge reactors\"?", "answer": "Akihisa Matsuda"}
{"qid": "39", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"crystal structure of 1 aminocyclopropane 1 carboxylate deaminase from hansenula saturnus\" and paper \"palladium nanoparticle catalyzed 1 7 palladium migration involving c h activation followed by intramolecular amination regioselective synthesis of n1 arylbenzotriazoles and an evaluation of their inhibitory activity toward indoleamine 2 3 dioxygenase\"?", "answer": "Hiroshi Sugimoto"}
{"qid": "40", "question": "Who has collaborated most frequently with author Sydney M. Zaremba?", "answer": "Lydia M. Gregoret"}
{"qid": "41", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Johannes M. Dieterich? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "Emily A. Carter"}
{"qid": "42", "question": "Who has collaborated most frequently with author Xavier de la Torre?", "answer": "Francesco Botr\u00e8"}
{"qid": "43", "question": "Who has collaborated most frequently with author Barry M. Willardson?", "answer": "Jorge Cu\u00e9llar"}
{"qid": "44", "question": "With whom did author Ryan C. Kramb have the highest number of collaborations?", "answer": "Charles F. Zukoski"}
{"qid": "45", "question": "Who can be defined as the closest collaborator of author J. Blaisdell, according to the number of their joint works?", "answer": "J.F. Haskell"}
{"qid": "46", "question": "Who can be defined as the closest collaborator of author Glen L. Holden, according to the number of their joint works?", "answer": "David L. Freeman"}
{"qid": "47", "question": "With whom did author Y. Katsuma have the highest number of collaborations?", "answer": "K. Shimakawa"}
{"qid": "48", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Alain Kumps? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "Yves L\u00e9once Mardens"}
{"qid": "49", "question": "With whom did author Georgios P. Danezis have the highest number of collaborations?", "answer": "Constantinos A. Georgiou"}
{"qid": "50", "question": "How many collaborators does author Hung-Chun Tsai have in 2008", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "51", "question": "Can you tell me the number of people Ma Xue collaborated with in 2016?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "52", "question": "What is the total count of collaborators for Fumihiro Watanabe in 2017?", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "53", "question": "What is the total count of collaborators for Jun Zhu in 2018?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "54", "question": "In 2019, how many co-workers did author Krishna Gavvala collaborate with?", "answer": "19"}
{"qid": "55", "question": "How many collaborators does author Chi Choi have in 2003", "answer": "14"}
{"qid": "56", "question": "In 2001, how many co-workers did author C Glasson collaborate with?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "57", "question": "What is the total count of collaborators for Z. D. Zeng in 1991?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "58", "question": "During 1994, how many individuals did S. Subba Rao work with on their publications?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "59", "question": "Can you tell me the number of people Yujun Yin collaborated with in 2019?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "60", "question": "How many joint papers do Rajendra Prasad Paitandi and Rakesh K. Gupta have?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "61", "question": "What is the count of papers co-written by Robert J. Gorelick and Ioulia Rouzina?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "62", "question": "How many papers did Michael J. Evans and Ulrich H\u00e4ussermann write together?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "63", "question": "How many joint papers do Bianka K\u00f3tai and Markku Leskel\u00e4 have?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "64", "question": "How many joint papers do P\u00e1l El\u00f6di and Roger Simonsson have?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "65", "question": "How many joint papers do Mohanad Shkoor and Helmut Reinke have?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "66", "question": "How many joint papers do Lauren C. Purington and Jillian Helen Broadbear have?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "67", "question": "Can you tell me the number of papers authored by Yinping Zheng and Huiwen Zhu together?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "68", "question": "Can you tell me the number of papers authored by Zijian Xie and Sankaridrug M. Periyasamy together?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "69", "question": "How many papers did Carolyn Koester and Janel E. Owens write together?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "70", "question": "What is the number of papers that reference the paper \"factors affecting cellulose and hemicellulose hydrolysis of alkali treated brewers spent grain by fusarium oxysporum enzyme extract\"?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "71", "question": "How many times has the paper \"total synthesis and stereochemical reassignment of the indole alkaloid vinoxine\" been cited in other papers?", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "72", "question": "Can you tell me the amount of papers that cite \"fluorine 19 nmr relaxation and water penetration in surfactant micelles\"?", "answer": "15"}
{"qid": "73", "question": "Can you tell me the amount of papers that cite \"reduction by intracellular calcium chelation of acetylcholine secretion without occluding the effects of adenosine at frog motor nerve endings\"?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "74", "question": "How many times has the paper \"tuning of thermo responsive self assembly monolayers on gold for cell type specific control of adhesion\" been cited in other papers?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "75", "question": "What is the number of papers that reference the paper \"size controlled growth of cdse nanocrystals in microfluidic reactors\"?", "answer": "25"}
{"qid": "76", "question": "What is the number of papers that reference the paper \"solid state absorption spectroscopy of alkyl substituted oligothiophenes\"?", "answer": "37"}
{"qid": "77", "question": "How many times has the paper \"alloying effects of cosputtered gold platinum thin films on the oxygen reduction reaction in acidic electrolyte\" been cited in other papers?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "78", "question": "Can you tell me the amount of papers that cite \"insulin membrane interactions and membrane fluidity changes\"?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "79", "question": "What is the number of papers that reference the paper \"effect of sulfhydryl group modification on the activities of 5 oxo l prolinase\"?", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "80", "question": "How many references does the paper \"nucleophilic trapping of \u03c0 allylpalladium intermediates generated by carbopalladation of bicyclopropylidene a novel three component reaction\" have?", "answer": "12"}
{"qid": "81", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers cited by \"staining of fluid catalytic cracking catalysts localising bronsted acidity within a single catalyst particle\"?", "answer": "21"}
{"qid": "82", "question": "How many papers does paper \"perturbing the copper iii hydroxide unit through ligand structural variation\" cite?", "answer": "62"}
{"qid": "83", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers cited by \"synthesis of indium nanoparticles digestive ripening under mild conditions\"?", "answer": "21"}
{"qid": "84", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers cited by \"electrolytic partial fluorination of organic compounds part 48 anodic fluorination of 2 cyano 1 methylpyrrole\"?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "85", "question": "How many papers does paper \"modification in the composition and metabolic properties of human low density and high density lipoproteins by different dietary fats\" cite?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "86", "question": "How many references does the paper \"electrowinning al from al2s3 in molten salt\" have?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "87", "question": "How many references does the paper \"evaluation of the intrinsic photocatalytic oxidation kinetics of indoor air pollutants\" have?", "answer": "9"}
{"qid": "88", "question": "How many papers does paper \"a comparative kinetic study of ethylene polymerization mediated by iron cobalt and chromium catalysts bearing the same n n n bis imino trihydroquinoline\" cite?", "answer": "13"}
{"qid": "89", "question": "How many papers does paper \"function of xenopus cystic fibrosis transmembrane conductance regulator cftr cl channels and use of human xenopus chimeras to investigate the pore properties of cftr\" cite?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "90", "question": "What is the most frequently referenced paper from author E. Bulska?", "answer": "different sample introduction systems for the multaneous determination of as sb and se by microwave induced plasma atomic emission spectrometry"}
{"qid": "91", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author Zhongjun Liu?", "answer": "simvastatin induces osteoblastic differentiation and inhibits adipocytic differentiation in mouse bone marrow stromal cells"}
{"qid": "92", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author Salvatore Crapanzano?", "answer": "effect of v in la2nixv1 xo4 \u03b4 on selective oxidative dehydrogenation of propane"}
{"qid": "93", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author N. Yahata?", "answer": "a method for copper film deposition with cl2 plasma"}
{"qid": "94", "question": "What is the most frequently referenced paper from author Johanna Heinola?", "answer": "sensitive bioaffinity assays with individual microparticles and time resolved fluorometry"}
{"qid": "95", "question": "Which paper by Bernhard Paulweber has received the most citations?", "answer": "plasma distribution of apoa iv in patients with coronary artery disease and healthy controls"}
{"qid": "96", "question": "Which paper by Masaaki Imasho has received the most citations?", "answer": "chiral synthesis of tri o methylimbricatine an etherified derivative of the starfish alkaloid imbricatine"}
{"qid": "97", "question": "What is the most frequently referenced paper from author Jeongrai Lee?", "answer": "characterization of catechol 2 3 dioxygenases"}
{"qid": "98", "question": "What is the most frequently referenced paper from author M. J. Hoskins?", "answer": "trap emission rates in gaas in the presence of surface acoustic waves"}
{"qid": "99", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author M. Hannah Degeling?", "answer": "directed molecular evolution reveals gaussia luciferase variants with enhanced light output stability"}
{"qid": "100", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers were written by Rajeev Aurora?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "101", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers were written by G. Sardin?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "102", "question": "What is the count of papers written by the author C. Wittig?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "103", "question": "How many papers did author John McKiernan write?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "104", "question": "How many papers did author T. Ishida write?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "105", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers were written by Huan Jin?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "106", "question": "Can you tell me the number of papers Yuval Oreg has written?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "107", "question": "What is the count of papers written by the author Ruyi He?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "108", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers were written by D. P. Gilmore?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "109", "question": "How many papers did author Samantha L. Young write?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "110", "question": "Which venue did Jason S. Kingsbury and E. J. Corey collaborate most?", "answer": "journal of the american chemical society"}
{"qid": "111", "question": "At what location did Yves Quenet and Jer\u00f4me Cassayre mostly work together?", "answer": "tetrahedron"}
{"qid": "112", "question": "Where was the primary place of collaboration for Karleon S. Callahan and John M. Harlan?", "answer": "journal of clinical investigation"}
{"qid": "113", "question": "Where did Cesar Clavero and Rosa A. Lukaszew most frequently join efforts?", "answer": "nano letters"}
{"qid": "114", "question": "At what location did Linlin Yang and Chunying Duan mostly work together?", "answer": "angewandte chemie"}
{"qid": "115", "question": "Where did Steven A. Milinkovi\u0107 and Olga S. Milanko most frequently join efforts?", "answer": "analytica chimica acta"}
{"qid": "116", "question": "Where did Dengwei He and Jiawei Gao most frequently join efforts?", "answer": "the faseb journal"}
{"qid": "117", "question": "Where was the primary place of collaboration for Liyu Li and Zhenguo Yang?", "answer": "journal of power sources"}
{"qid": "118", "question": "At what location did Sebastian Busch and Andr\u00e9s Henao mostly work together?", "answer": "physical chemistry chemical physics"}
{"qid": "119", "question": "Where was the primary place of collaboration for C\u00e1tia Gon\u00e7alves and Filipa A. Vicente?", "answer": "green chemistry"}
{"qid": "120", "question": "How many intermediaries does author Yuko Ueda need to make contact with author Ying Hu?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "121", "question": "How many people does author Delores M. Dochwat need to know at least to know author Garry L. Cantrell?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "122", "question": "What is the minimum number of people author Gregory King should know to be acquainted with author Robert A. Barford?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "123", "question": "What is the least number of people author Kouhei Nakagawa needs to know to reach author Rinku Majumder?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "124", "question": "What is the minimum number of people author Ann-Charlotte M. Toes should know to be acquainted with author Zsolt Szengyel?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "125", "question": "Through how many people does author Carles Bo need to connect in order to know author J. Vicente de Juli\u00e1n-Ortiz?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "126", "question": "What is the least number of people author G. Jeffrey Snyder needs to know to reach author Marie-Louise Saboungi?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "127", "question": "Through how many people does author Yi Tsong. Lin need to connect in order to know author Samuel Toba?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "128", "question": "What is the minimum number of people author Olexandr Karpenko should know to be acquainted with author Mehdi A. Beniddir?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "129", "question": "How many people does author Xin Cheng need to know at least to know author Yoshihiro Ishihara?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "130", "question": "Of the provided papers effect of hypoxia on nitric oxide production and its synthase gene expression in rat smooth muscle cells, kraft pulping of eucalyptus globulus kinetics of residual delignification, erratum to the strong hydrogen bonds in high density amorphous ice at high pressures chemical physics letters 349 2001 51 56, reversible room temperature ionic liquids amidinium carbamates derived from amidines and aliphatic primary amines with carbon dioxide, oxygen vacancy enhanced electrochemiluminescence sensing strategy using luminol thermally encapsulated in apoferritin as a transducer for biomarker immunoassay, mechanistic aspects of the catalytic reduction of dioxygen by cofacial metalloporphyrins, phenolic profile antioxidants and sensory acceptance of bioactive enhanced peanuts using ultrasound and uv, three new \u03b2 carbolines from the bermudian tunicate eudistoma olivaceum, visible to uv up conversion in er3 doped cadmium chloride and zinc chloride glasses, synthesis of selectively protected tri and hexaamine macrocycles, which one would be the best recommendation for inhibition of translation initiation by endotoxin and interferon gamma in skeletal muscle cells is nitric oxide synthase nos dependent readers? Please give the paper title instead of its ID.", "answer": "effect of hypoxia on nitric oxide production and its synthase gene expression in rat smooth muscle cells"}
{"qid": "131", "question": "Of the provided papers total synthesis of \u03b3 alkylidenebutenolides potent melanogenesis inhibitors from thai medicinal plant melodorum fruticosum, t cells with similar t cell receptor \u03b2 chain complementarity determining region 3 motifs infiltrate inflammatory lesions of synthetic peptides inducing rat autoimmune myocarditis, d295n mutant cathepsin d exerts a dominant negative effect in vitro by promoting alpha synuclein accumulation, short exposure to endotoxin increases the constriction induced by angiotensin ii in rat aorta, monte carlo simulations of polyelectrolytes at charged micelles 1 effects of chain flexibility, attenuated erythrocytic atp release is caused by extracellular hemoglobin, activity of human blood platelets in prothrombin and in factor x activation induced by ionophore a23187, structural dynamics in the resting and activated states of the voltage sensor of ci vsp from dipolar distance measurements, absorption of water in the active layer of reverse osmosis membranes, textures and phase transitions in langmuir monolayers of fatty acids a comparative brewster angle microscope and polarized fluorescence microscope study, which one would be the best recommendation for increased expression of procoagulant activity on the surface of human platelets exposed to heavy metal compounds readers? Please give the paper title instead of its ID.", "answer": "activity of human blood platelets in prothrombin and in factor x activation induced by ionophore a23187"}
{"qid": "132", "question": "Can you suggest a paper for readers of characterization of bovine rod outer segment g protein from the following selection: identification functional and structural characterization of novel aminoglycoside phosphotransferase aph 3 id from streptomyces rimosus subsp rimosus atcc 10970, a novel and efficient direct aldol condensation from ketones and aromatic aldehydes catalyzed by proline tea through a new pathway, interaction of co with cu cations co adsorption on cu2o 100, crystal structure and dynamic proton nmr of 1 2 bis pyridin 2 yl ethane n n bis 9 methylhypoxanthine n7 platinum ii dinitrate, the effect of electrostatic fields on an oligo ethylene glycol molecule dipole moments polarizabilities and field dissociation, bixalomer a novel phosphate binder with a small swelling index improves hyperphosphatemia in chronic kidney disease rat, purification and characterization of the gamma regulatory subunit of the cyclic gmp phosphodiesterase from retinal rod outer segments, solubility and sorption by soils of 8 2 fluorotelomer alcohol in water and cosolvent systems, structure function studies on the bacterial carbohydrate transporters enzymes ii of the phosphoenolpyruvate dependent phosphotransferase system, signal transduction pathway activity compensates dopamine d2 d3 receptor density changes in parkinson s disease a preliminary comparative human brain receptor autoradiography study with 3h raclopride and 35s gtp\u03b3s? Please respond with the title of the paper, not the ID.", "answer": "purification and characterization of the gamma regulatory subunit of the cyclic gmp phosphodiesterase from retinal rod outer segments"}
{"qid": "133", "question": "Of the provided papers synthesis of purine nucleoside amino acid conjugates and their photophysical properties, investigations of the dispersion of pd in h zsm 5, smectic demixing in the phase behavior and self assembly of a hydrogen bonded polymer with mesogenic side chains, breath by breath alveolar gas exchange, selective phosphate removal from water and wastewater using sorption process fundamentals and removal mechanisms, polymer grafted with asymmetrical dication ionic liquid as efficient and reusable catalysts for the synthesis of cyclic carbonates from co2 and expoxides, crystal structure of an rna quadruplex containing inosine tetrad implications for the roles of nh2 group in purine tetrads, key factors for optimum performance in phosphate removal from contaminated water by a fe mg la tri metal composite sorbent, structural characterization of l glutamate oxidase from streptomyces sp x 119 6, covalent binding of acetaldehyde to type iii collagen, which one would be the best recommendation for dilution of alveolar carbon dioxide during inspiration by the tidal volume inhaled readers? Please give the paper title instead of its ID.", "answer": "breath by breath alveolar gas exchange"}
{"qid": "134", "question": "Which paper should be recommended to the reader of paper quantitation isolation and characterization of human lipoprotein a? Please select from the candidate list new strategy for the synthesis of 3 substituted prolines, peptide ligands of pp60 c src sh2 domains a thermodynamic and structural study, organic molecule modulated phase evolution of inorganic mesostructures, probing thermodynamic aspects of electrochemically driven ion transfer processes across liquid liquid interfaces pure versus diluted redox liquids, high resolution fourier transform ion cyclotron resonance mass spectrometry with increased throughput for biomolecular analysis, human plasma lipoprotein a structural properties, application of volumetric electrodes to the recuperation of metals in industrial effluents iii potential distributions and design of radial field electrodes, dose dependent differences in the mutational profiles of 1r 2s 3s 4r 3 4 dihydroxy 1 2 epoxy 1 2 3 4 tetrahydrobenzo c phenanthrene and its less carcinogenic enantiomer, resonance enhancement of nonlinear optical scattering in monolayer protected gold clusters, triplet exciton generation and decay in a red polydiacetylene studied by femtosecond spectroscopy. Please answer the paper title rather than ID.", "answer": "human plasma lipoprotein a structural properties"}
{"qid": "135", "question": "Which paper should be recommended to the reader of paper probing the secondary structure of the essential linker domain in the serine chemotaxis receptor using solid state nmr? Please select from the candidate list low resolution structural determination of lipoprotein6 6 a membrane component of borrelia burgdorferi 753 2, unprecedented binding cooperativity between cu i and cu ii in the copper resistance protein copk from cupriavidus metallidurans ch34 implications from structural studies by nmr spectroscopy and x ray crystallography, sulfonium salts as lanthanide shift donors in pmr amd cmr spectroscopy, lipophilic character of cardiac glycosides, glyca a composite nuclear magnetic resonance biomarker of systemic inflammation, cp co 2mn 2pbstbu completion of an isoelectronic series of binuclear complexes containing trigonal planar coordinated main group elements, phosphinoalkylsilyl complexes 6 isolation of a silyl complex of iridium i crystal and molecular structure of dicarbonyl triphenylphosphine diphenylphosphino ethyl dimethylsilyl iridium, insight into the efficient tsna capturer derived from zeolite h\u03b2, secondary structure of the hamp domain of the e coli serine receptor by solid state nmr, determination of selenium iv by differential pulse voltammetry of the 3 3 diaminobenzidine piazselenol. Please answer the paper title rather than ID.", "answer": "secondary structure of the hamp domain of the e coli serine receptor by solid state nmr"}
{"qid": "136", "question": "Can you suggest a paper for readers of tnf alpha induces mmp 9 expression via a tnfr1 c src egfr pdgfr dependent pathway in rat cardiomyoblastic cells from the following selection: chemistry of xanthorrhizol synthesis of several bisabolane sesquiterpenoids from xanthorrhizol, immune synapse formation determines interaction forces between t cells and antigen presenting cells measured by atomic force microscopy, overexpression of mitochondrial superoxide dismutase in mice protects the retina from diabetes induced oxidative stress, alkali metal adsorption on al 111, synthesis of polysubstituted anilines using the diels alder reaction of methyl 5 aminofuroate, abstract sy44 04 targeted mrm mass spectrometry enables highly multiplexed quantification of cell signaling in response to dna damage, comparative study of the sugar chains of alkaline phosphatases purified from rat liver and rat ah 130 hepatoma cells occurrence of fucosylated high mannose type and hybrid type sugar chains, ab initio cluster model approach to the chemisorption of hydrogen on mercury, tnf alpha induced mmp 9 expression via src egfr akt p300 nf kappa b and histone acetylation in tracheal smooth muscle cells, a random method for theoretical estimation of rbc osmotic damage in removing cpas from cryopreserved blood with hollow fiber modules closed loop blood flow mode? Please respond with the title of the paper, not the ID.", "answer": "tnf alpha induced mmp 9 expression via src egfr akt p300 nf kappa b and histone acetylation in tracheal smooth muscle cells"}
{"qid": "137", "question": "Of the provided papers an early elevation of diacylglycerol and phosphatidate in regenerating liver, co elimination processes over promoter free hydroxyapatite supported palladium catalysts, identification and evaluation of antioxidants defatted camellia oleifera seeds by isopropanol salting out pretreatment, determination of cisplatin and its hydrolytic metabolite in human serum by capillary electrophoresis techniques, catalytic hydrodehalogenation over supported gold electron transfer versus hydride transfer, can mediated oxidative addition of 2 hydroxynaphthoquinone to dienes a facile synthesis of naphthofurandiones, improved spectral resolution in cosy 1h nmr spectra of proteins via double quantum filtering, influence of a commercial formulation of tridemorph on methane production and oxidation in a tropical rice soil, study of the chromonic liquid crystalline phases of bis n n diethylaminoethyl perylene 3 4 9 10 tetracarboxylic diimide dihydrochloride by polarized optical microscopy and 2h nmr spectroscopy, the ile 84 ser amino acid substitution in transthyretin interferes with the interaction with plasma retinol binding protein, which one would be the best recommendation for capillary electrophoresis of platinum group elements analytical speciation and biochemical studies readers? Please give the paper title instead of its ID.", "answer": "determination of cisplatin and its hydrolytic metabolite in human serum by capillary electrophoresis techniques"}
{"qid": "138", "question": "Of the provided papers exposure to fullerene c60 nanoparticles impairs lung mechanics and mitochondrial function, renal sulfatides sphingoid base dependent localization and region specific compensation of cers2 dysfunction, laser desorption mass spectrometry of chemically and electrochemically prepared poly 2 vinylthiophene, the interaction of melittin with calmodulin and its tryptic fragments, evaluation of accelerated dechlorination of p p ddt in acidic paddy soil, simple and efficient system for combined solar energy harvesting and reversible hydrogen storage, structural attributes of mammalian prion infectivity insights from studies with synthetic prions, diffusion of atoms and dimers on metal surfaces, regio and stereoselective copper catalyzed carbozincation reactions of alkynyl sulfoximines and sulfones, neuronal nitric oxide synthase membrane phospholipid interactions, which one would be the best recommendation for structural insights into the interaction between prion protein and heparin readers? Please give the paper title instead of its ID.", "answer": "structural attributes of mammalian prion infectivity insights from studies with synthetic prions"}
{"qid": "139", "question": "Can you suggest a paper for readers of 2 monopalmitin treatment induces a greater inflammatory response than palmitate in 3t3 l1 adipocytes from the following selection: reversible inactivation of rat liver inorganic pyrophosphatase by substrate and its analogs, ricin transport distinguishes between central and peripheral neurons, synthesis spectroscopic and a zindo study of cis and trans x2 bis 4 4 dicarboxylic acid 2 2 bipyridine ruthenium ii complexes x cl h2o ncs, differentiation of 3t3 l1 adipocytes with arachidonic acid increases inflammatory markers, surface charge effects on ion conduction in ion channels, 28 membrane protein molecular weight determined by low angle laser light scattering photometry coupled with high performance gel chromatography, effect of chain length on the adsorption behavior of n alkanes in ferrierite, direct dynamics simulations of the unimolecular decomposition of the randomly excited 1ch2o2 criegee intermediate comparison with 3ch2 3o2 reaction dynamics, comparison of the engulfment and the interaction by exchange with the mean micromixing models, local structural preferences of calpastatin the intrinsically unstructured protein inhibitor of calpain? Please respond with the title of the paper, not the ID.", "answer": "differentiation of 3t3 l1 adipocytes with arachidonic acid increases inflammatory markers"}
